DANIEL REY

+63-966-2674-689 · <u>danielrey.vercel.app</u> · <u>@danielrey</u> · <u>reyvillanuevadaniel@gmail.com</u> L4 B8 Ecology Subdivision Vinzons Camarines Norte

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I have created various Web Apps and Android Apps when developing these I have implemented complex algorithm and scale the product according to the clients need. Additionally I have integrated an API to both web and mobile app which leads me to become a better developer and understand the underlying conflict. With almost 2 years of experience in developing complex application I have been exposed to many problems so I can guaranteed that I will fullfil my job if you hire me as a developer.

SKILLS

Javascript | HTML | CSS | React | Tailwind | NextJS

Java (JavaFX, JavaME, JavaSE) | Firebase | RESTful API | MySQL | PostgreSQL | SQLite Figma | Adobe XD | Postman

EXPERIENCE

Thesis: An android based app for maternal health reproductive Android Developer

2022 - 2023

- Features: Video Recommendations containing maternal health videos, Realtime Chat w/ notification for seamless chat and experience, Chatbot for emergency questions with reliable response. Online schedule consultation for hassle free user.
- I received Senior BSCS: SE of the year 2023 award and our thesis awarded as Best Thesis
- I used Java, Firebase, SQLite, Adobe XD, Postman, and GCP

Fastlane Start-up Company (Intern)

March 2022 - May 2022

Backend Developer

- Maintain the existing software by developing modularized models and business logic which allowed for easy unit testing.
- Migrating the database from SQLite to PostgreSQL.
- We used Python Django, HTML, CSS(SCSS, Bootstrap), JS
- Maintain Point of Sale and Credit Management for Fastlane client.

Freelance

August 2020 - January 2022

Frontend Developer

- Creates UI/UX using Figma and Adobe XD
- · Makes an interactive UI with the latest frontend technologies.
- Develops Ph Online Lotto, Landing Page, Personal Site and Blog Site.
- Creates optimized algorithm for a better User Experience.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2019 - 2023

Mabini Colleges Inc.

CERTIFICATES

<u>Backend Developer - Internship</u> <u>Bootstrap Certificat</u>ions

HTML and CSS Certifications